Guide to the Katherine S. Dreier Papers / Societe Anonyme Archive
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Katherine S. Dreier: Correspondence, 1906-1952; Series I; 16; (41 boxes)
  - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE
    - Clough, Frederika H., 1949, 1951, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 236)
    - Coady, R. J., 1918 (Box 9, Folder 237)
    - Coates, Robert E., 1938, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 238)
    - Cochran, Aso Neith Neypá, 1923-32, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 239)
    - Coleman-Meerkerk, Inc., 1938-42 (Box 9, Folder 240)
    - Collectors of American Art, Inc., 1938 Mar 30 (Box 9, Folder 241)
    - College Art Association of America, 1932-48 (Box 9, Folder 242)
    - College Women's Club (Schenectady, N.Y.), 1923-24 (Box 9, Folder 243)
    - Collins, Frank H., 1927 (Box 9, Folder 244)
    - Colony Club, 1920-37, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 245)
    - Colten Photos, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 246)
    - Columbia University, 1928-50 (Box 9, Folder 247)
    - Columbus Gallery of Fine Arts, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 248)
    - Committee of 48 (U.S.), n.d. (Box 9, Folder 249)
    - Connoisseur, 1926 Sep 1 (Box 9, Folder 250)
    - Contemporary Arts, 1931-39 (Box 9, Folder 251)
    - Contemporary Arts Center (Cincinnati, Ohio), 1948 (Box 9, Folder 252)
    - Coogler, Mary A., 1937-42, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 253-254)
    - Cook, Nancy, 1931, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 255)
    - Coolidge, Calvin, 1927 May 5 (Box 9, Folder 256)
      From KDS regarding China.
    - Cooperative Mural Workshops, 1915-18 (Box 9, Folder 257)
    - Corbett, Harvey Wiley, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 258)
    - Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1929 Dec 23
      See: Oversize, box 131, folder 2875
    - Cosmopolitan Club, New York, 1920-27 (Box 9, Folder 259)
    - Cournand, E., 1926-27 (Box 9, Folder 260)
    - Covert, John R., 1923-49, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 261)
      See also: Society of Independent Artists (New York, N.Y.), box 33, folders 953-954
    - Cowell, Henry, 1927, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 262)
      See also: New Music Society of California, box 26, folder 761
      See also: Pan American Association of Composers, Inc., box 28, folder 809
      See also: B. W. Walton, box 36, folder 1078
    - Cowles, Edith, 1923, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 263)
    - Cowles, Genevieve Cowles, Mildred
    - Crandall, Carlin, 1945, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 264)
    - Creative Art, 1927, 1931 (Box 9, Folder 265)
    - Crothers, Rachel, 1926-39, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 266)
    - Crotti, Jean, 1927, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 267)
    - Crouse, Russell M., 1920 (Box 10, Folder 268)
    - Crowninshield, Frank, 1941 Jun 11 (Box 10, Folder 269)
      See also: Box 87, folder 2218
    - Crowther, Bosley, 1948 Apr 27 (Box 10, Folder 270)
    - "D" general, 1919-50, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 271-272)
    - Danbury News-Times, 1937, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 273)
    - Dance Magazine, 1930-31 (Box 10, Folder 274)
    - Daniel Gallery, 1923-27, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 275)
    - Darnton, Maida C., 1924-39, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 276-277)
    - Daugherty, James Henry, 1918-51, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 278-279)
    - Davies, Arthur B., 1920-26, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 280)
    - Davis, Stuart, 1926-51 (Box 10, Folder 281)
    - Davis, Wyatt, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 282)
    - De Maré, Rolf, 1937, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 283)
    - Dean, Edward, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 284)
    - Dearstyne, Howard, 1931-45, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 285-286)
    - Dearstyne, Maria, 1937-43, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 287)
    - Decorators Club, Inc., 1939 (Box 10, Folder 288)
    - Dellfant, Max, 1925, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 289)
    - Delphic Studios, 1931-42, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 290)
    - Denks, F., 1921-25, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 291)
    - Denver Art Museum, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 292)
    - Depero, Fortunato, 1929 (Box 10, Folder 293)
    - Dermée, Paul, 1928 Jan 24 (Box 10, Folder 294)
    - Detroit Institute of Arts, 1921-30 (Box 10, Folder 295)
    - Detwiller, Frederick K., 1925-51 (Box 10, Folder 296)
      See also: Artists of Carnegie Hall, Inc., box 3, folders 71-72
    - Dial, 1920-26 (Box 10, Folder 297)
    - Diller, Burgoyne, 1946-50 (Box 10, Folder 298)
      See also: Oversize, box 118, folder 2794
    - Dillingham, William P., 1919-20 (Box 10, Folder 299)
    - Doesburg, Alexander van, 1926, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 300)
    - Doesburg, Nelly van, 1947-51, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 301)
    - Domela, 1927, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 302)
    - Dominick, Elizabeth P., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 303)
    - Dorner, Alexander, 1938-50 (Box 11, Folder 304-305)
    - Dorner, Lydia, 1938 Oct 7
    - Dottori, Gerardo, 1926, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 306)
    - Downes, Edward, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 307)
    - Downes, Louise, 1938, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 308)
    - Downtown Gallery (New York, N.Y.), 1930-49 (Box 11, Folder 309)
    - Drei Masken Verlag, 1931-38, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 310-312)
    - Drewes, Werner, 1933-38, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 313-314)
    - Drewes, Margarete
    - Du Pont, Alfred Victor, 1940 (Box 12, Folder 315)
    - Duchamp, L., 1919-23 (Box 12, Folder 316)
    - Duchamp, Marcel, 1917-52, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 317-326)
    - Duchamp, Suzanne, 1927-49, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 327)
      See also: Box 77, folders 1982-1983
    - Dudensing, Leroy, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 328)
    - Dudensing, Valentine, 1927-42, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 329)
    - Duncan, Isadora
      See: Elizabeth Duncan-Schule, box 13, folder 343
    - Dunford, Nelson, 1950 Apr 3 (Box 12, Folder 330)
    - Dunn, Charlotte, 1941, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 331)
    - Dunn, Richard, 1942-44 (Box 12, Folder 332)
    - Dzubas, Friedel, 1947-51, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 333-334)
    - "E" general, 1913-51, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 335)
    - E. Weyhe, 1920-50 (Box 13, Folder 336)
    - Eaves Costume Co., 1927 (Box 13, Folder 337)
    - Ecke, Alice Beeson, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 338)
    - Eddy, Arthur Jerome (Mrs.), 1922-23 (Box 13, Folder 339)
    - Edward W. Hazen Foundation (Box 13, Folder 340)
    - Egner, Arthur F., 1939 (Box 13, Folder 341)
    - Eilshemius, Louis M., 1920-32, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 342)
      See also: Oversize, box 128, folder 2872
    - Elizabeth Duncan-Schule, 1916-30, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 343)
    - Elliot, Laura, 1935, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 344)
    - Encyclopedia Britannica, 1928-29 (Box 13, Folder 345)
    - Equitable Trust Company of New York, 1926 (Box 13, Folder 346)
      Includes receipts to Constantin Brancusi.
    - Erbslöh, Adolf, 1922-28, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 347)
    - Erkelenz, Anton, 1925, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 348)
    - Ernst, Max, 1920-26, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 349)
    - Exposition of Indian Tribal Arts, Inc., 1930 Nov 10 (Box 13, Folder 350)
    - "F" general, 1924-48, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 351-352)
    - F. A. C. Prestel (Firm: Frankfurt am Main, Germany), n.d. (Box 13, Folder 353)
    - Faculty Club (New Haven, Conn.), 1942 (Box 13, Folder 354)
    - Feininger, Lyonel, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 355)
      See also: Alexander Dorner (1950 Mar 9), box 11, folder 305
    - Felton, Connie, 1939 Jul 28 (Box 13, Folder 356)
    - Felton, Major, 1939, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 357)
    - Ferargil Galleries, 1926-27, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 358)
    - Fifth Avenue Bank of New York
    - Filla, Emil, 1926-27, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 359)
    - Fitzsimmons, James, 1949-50, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 360)
    - Flexner, Abraham, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 361)
      See also: Box 85, folder 2192
    - Floyd, Louise Adams, 1939, 1945, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 362)
      See also: League for Industrial Democracy, box 21, folder 615
    - Fogg Art Museum, 1929 Dec 20
    - Ford, Julia Ellsworth, 1933, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 363)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1948 Jun 17 (Box 13, Folder 364)
    - Foreign Press Service, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 365)
    - Forum (New York, N.Y.), 1925-37 (Box 13, Folder 366)
    - Foundation for Integrated Education, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 367)
    - Fox, Catherine J. D., 1925-45, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 368)
    - Fox, William Henry
      See: Brooklyn Museum, box 6, folders 152-157
      See: Catherine J. D. Fox, box 13, folder 368
    - Franck, Peter, 1925-33, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 369)
    - Freeman, 1920-21 (Box 13, Folder 370)
    - Fried, Rose
      See: Pinacotheca, box 29, folders 838-840
      See: Box 83, folder 2105
    - Friends of Art (Baltimore, Md.), 1923 (Box 13, Folder 371)
    - Fuhs, J., 1918, 1920, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 372)
    - Fulkerson, Idee, 1949-51 (Box 13, Folder 373)
    - Fuller, Lucia, 1918, 1920, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 374)
    - "G" general, 1917-48, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 375-376)
    - Gabo, Miriam, 1937-51, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 377)
    - Gabo, Naum, 1928-50, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 378)
      See also: Miriam Gabo, box 14, folder 377
    - Gadski, Johanna, 1931-32, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 379)
    - Gage, M., 1945, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 380)
    - Gaiss, Anna, 1939 (Box 14, Folder 381)
    - Galerie del Vecchio, 1912 Oct 24 (Box 14, Folder 382)
    - Galerie Ferdinand Möller, 1922 Oct 9 (Box 14, Folder 383)
    - Galerie René Gimpel, 1936 (Box 14, Folder 384)
    - Galerie Van Diemen & Co., 1922-23, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 385)
    - Gallatin, A. E., 1926-40, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 386)
    - Gallup, Donald Clifford
    - Gargallo, Pablo, 1926 (Box 14, Folder 387)
    - Gaulois, Paul, 1925-31, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 388-390)
      See also: Rohner, Gehrig & Co., Inc., box 30, folder 883
    - Gawthorpe, Mary, 1930-50 (Box 14, Folder 391)
    - General Committee for the City and County of New-York, 1923 (Box 14, Folder 392)
    - George, George L., 1944 Dec 21 (Box 14, Folder 393)
    - George F. Of, Inc., 1920-51, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 394-397)
    - George Grady Press, 1931 Mar 26 (Box 14, Folder 398)
    - George Walter Vincent Smith Art Museum, 1937-43, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 399-401)
    - Georges, Madame, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 402)
    - Germany. Botschaft (U.S.), 1926-27 (Box 15, Folder 403)
    - Giedion-Welcker, Carola, 1950-51 (Box 15, Folder 404)
    - Giersberg, Therese, 1920-28 (Box 15, Folder 405)
    - Gilbert Rohde, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 406)
    - Gilder, Rosamond, 1927, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 407)
    - Glackens, William J., 1917 (Box 15, Folder 408)
    - Glarner, Fritz, 1946-51 (Box 15, Folder 409)
    - Gleizes, Albert, 1926, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 410)
    - Godewols, Ludwig, 1920-21 (Box 15, Folder 411)
    - Gogh, Elisabeth du Quesne van, 1912-27, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 412-413)
    - Goldenweiser, Alexander, 1923, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 414)
    - Goldthwaite, Anne, 1927, 1929, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 415)
    - Goldthwaite, Lucille, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 416)
    - Goltz, Hans, Graf von der, 1922, 1924, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 417)
    - Gommi and Company, 1926 (Box 15, Folder 418)
    - Goodspeed, Elizabeth F., 1937-38, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 419)
    - Gotham Book Mart, 1950 Nov 13 (Box 15, Folder 420)
    - Graduates Club (New Haven, Conn.), n.d. (Box 15, Folder 421)
    - Graham, Constance, 1938-39 (Box 15, Folder 422)
      See also: John Graham, box 15, folders 423-424
    - Graham, John, 1928-49, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 423-424)
      See also: Constance Graham, box 15, folder 422
    - Grand Rapids Art Museum, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 425)
    - Grantham, Godfrey
      See: Box 77, folder 1985
    - Grantham, Sandy, 1928-29, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 426)
      See also: Box 77, folder 1986
    - Gray, Cleve, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 427)
    - Gray, Howard, 1926-27 (Box 15, Folder 428)
    - Gray, William G., 1931, 1940, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 429)
    - Griffin, Christine, 1923-43, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 430-431)
    - Gris, Juan, 1927 May 16 (Box 16, Folder 432)
    - Grohmann, Will, 1927, 1930 (Box 16, Folder 433)
    - Gropius, Walter, 1923-50, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 434)
    - Grossman, Moses H., 1923 (Box 16, Folder 435)
    - Grosz, George, 1920, 1922 (Box 16, Folder 436)
    - Guaranty Trust Company of New York, 1917 (Box 16, Folder 437)
    - Guggenheim, Peggy, 1942, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 438)
    - Guild Art Gallery, 1936, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 439)
    - Gutbier, Ludwig L., 1931, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 440)
    - Gutfreund, Oto, 1926-27 (Box 16, Folder 441)
    - Gwozdecki, Gustave de, 1923 (Box 16, Folder 442)
    - "H" general, 1916-51, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 443-445)
    - H. Beyer Detmold, 1924 (Box 16, Folder 446)
    - H. Kempner (Firm), 1920 (Box 16, Folder 447)
    - Hagenbach, Marguerite
      See: Marguerite Arp, box 3, folder 61
    - Hahn Brothers, 1936-37, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 448)
    - Halicka, Alice, 1949, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 449)
      See also: Helena Rubinstein, box 30, folder 890
    - Halle Bros. Co., 1927 Jul 26 (Box 16, Folder 450)
    - Hambidge, Mary Crovatte, 1931 (Box 16, Folder 451)
    - Hamburg-Amerikanische Packetfahrt- Actien-Gesellschaft, 1936 (Box 16, Folder 452)
    - Hamilton, George Heard, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 453)
    - Hamilton, Polly
      See also: Yale University Art Gallery, box 39, folders 1125-1137
    - Hamlin, Charlotte, 1949, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 454)
    - Hamlin, Chauncey, 1926, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 455)
    - Hamlin, Emily, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 456)
      See also: Chauncey Hamlin, box 16, folder 455
    - Hamlin, Marston A., 1947 (Box 16, Folder 457)
    - Hamlin, Ruth, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 458)
    - Hammond, Emily V., 1930-46, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 459)
    - Hanfstaengl, Eberhard, 1950, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 460)
    - Hanfstaengl, Edgar, 1932, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 461)
    - Hanfstaengl, Erna, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 462)
    - Hanfstaengl, Katherine, 1919-39, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 463-467)
    - Harcourt Brace & Company, 1927 (Box 16, Folder 468)
    - Hard, Anne, 1925-37, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 469)
    - Hard, William, 1941-42 (Box 16, Folder 470)
    - Harper's Magazine, 1913 Jun 6 (Box 17, Folder 471)
    - Harris, Lawren, 1926-50, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 472)
    - Harris, Marguerite Tjader, 1937, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 473)
    - Harrison, Preston, 1926-27 (Box 17, Folder 474)
    - Hartford Seminary Foundation, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 475)
    - Hartt, Frederick, 1938-50, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 476-478)
    - Hartt, Peggy
    - Hartwell, Jobson, and Kibbee, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 479)
    - Heap, Jane
      See: Inter Arts, box 18, folder 523
      See: Little Review, box 22, folder 641
    - Hekking, William M., 1935-41, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 480-486)
      See also: Albright Art Gallery (Buffalo, N.Y.), box 1, folders 23-24
    - Henniker-Heaton, Raymond
      See: Worcester Art Museum, box 37, folders 1117-1118
      See: Box 84, folder 2128
    - Henry Art Gallery, 1927-37 (Box 17, Folder 487)
    - Hess, Inez Elizabeth, 1944-50, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 488)
    - Heythum, Antonin, 1946-47, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 489)
    - Heythum, Charlotta
    - Heywood, Florence, 1938-49, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 490)
    - Highet, Gilbert, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 491)
    - Hildebrandt, Hans, 1927-50, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 492-494)
      See also: Lily Hildebrandt, box 18, folder 495
    - Hildebrandt, Lily, 1927-52, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 495)
      See also: Hans Hildebrandt, box 18, folders 492-494
    - Hillyer, Mary W., 1941 (Box 18, Folder 496)
    - Hind, Charles Lewis, 1920 Nov 29 (Box 18, Folder 497)
    - Hirshhorn, Joseph H., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 498)
    - Hoeland, Kaete, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 499)
    - Hofmann, Hans, 1920 (Box 18, Folder 500)
    - Holding, Eileen, 1937-38 (Box 18, Folder 501)
    - Holtzman, Harry, 1944-50 (Box 18, Folder 502)
    - Hope, Henry R., 1948, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 503)
    - Horter, Earl, 1927, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 504)
    - Hotchkiss School, 1941 (Box 18, Folder 505)
    - Houghton, Mifflin and Company, 1912-36 (Box 18, Folder 506-507)
    - Howard, Lucille, 1934-35, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 508-509)
    - Hubbard, Ernest, 1926 (Box 18, Folder 510)
    - Hudson Forwarding & Shipping Co., Inc., 1937 (Box 18, Folder 511)
    - Huebsch, B. W., 1921, 1923, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 512)
    - Human Events, 1948 Sep 20 (Box 18, Folder 513)
    - Hume, Edward H., 1923, 1931 (Box 18, Folder 514)
    - Huntington, Archer Milton, 1920-49 (Box 18, Folder 515)
    - Huntington, Margaret W., 1923-41, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 516)
    - Huss, Henry Holden, 1939 (Box 18, Folder 517)
    - Hyperion Press, 1942, 1945 (Box 18, Folder 518)
    - "I" general, 1924-26, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 519)
    - Ickes, Harold L., 1950 Jul 10 (Box 18, Folder 520)
    - Ickes, Jane, 1947 Sep 10
    - Independent Forwarding Co., Inc., 1927 (Box 18, Folder 521)
    - Institute of Contemporary Art (Boston, Mass.), 1949 (Box 18, Folder 522)
    - Inter Arts, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 523)
    - International Business Machines Corporation, 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 524)
    - International Institute of China, 1927 Sep 6 (Box 18, Folder 525)
    - International Studio, 1913-25 (Box 18, Folder 526)
    - Inter-racial Council (New York, N.Y.), 1920 Mar 29 (Box 18, Folder 527)
    - Ireland, Alleyne, 1939 Feb 7 (Box 18, Folder 528)
    - Ives, Harmony Twichell, 1945 Jan 23 (Box 18, Folder 529)
    - "J" general, 1913-50, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 530)
    - J.-F.-Schröder-Bank, 1922 Nov 3 (Box 19, Folder 531)
    - J. J. O'Brien & Son, 1920-45, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 532-533)
    - J. M. Dent & Sons, 1931-33, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 534)
    - Jackson, William S., 1938 (Box 19, Folder 535)
    - Jacobi, Rudolf, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 536)
    - Jacob's Pillow Dance Festival, 1941-48, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 537)
      See also: Box 62, folders 1675-1676
    - Jacques Seligmann & Co., 1938, 1946 (Box 19, Folder 538)
    - Janis, Sidney, 1932-50 (Box 19, Folder 539)
    - Janowitz, Sidney
      See: Sidney Janis, box 19, folder 539
    - Jarecka, Louise Llewellyn, 1949, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 540)
    - Jawlensky, Alexej von, 1923 Jan 12 (Box 19, Folder 541)
    - Jewell, Edward Alden, 1935 Feb 11 (Box 19, Folder 542)
    - Jewish Communal Center. Literary Forum, 1922-23 (Box 19, Folder 543)
    - John Becker (Firm), 1931, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 544)
    - John H. Vanderpoel Art Association, 1936-48 (Box 19, Folder 545)
    - John J. Shore Co., Inc., 1926 (Box 19, Folder 546)
    - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1931-35 (Box 19, Folder 547-548)
    - John Wanamaker (Firm), 1925, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 549)
    - Johnson, Alvin Saunders, 1933, 1941 (Box 19, Folder 550)
      See also: New School for Social Research (New York, N.Y.), box 26, folders 763-764
    - Jones, David Taylor, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 551)
    - Jordan, Heinrich P., 1939 (Box 19, Folder 552)
    - Joseph A. Mrazek Moving and Storage Co., Inc., 1948-49 (Box 19, Folder 553)
    - Julien Levy Gallery (New York, N.Y.), n.d. (Box 19, Folder 554)
    - "K" general, 1914-50, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 555-556)
    - Kádár, Béla, 1927-29 (Box 19, Folder 557)
    - Kahin, Carmody, Schramm & Kellogg, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 558)
    - Kahn, Otto Hermann, 1923 (Box 19, Folder 559)
    - Kaiser Wilhelm Museum Krefeld, 1929 (Box 19, Folder 560)
    - Kakabadze, Davit, 1926-27 (Box 19, Folder 561)
    - Kallir, Otto, 1925-26 (Box 19, Folder 562)
    - Kamys, Walter, 1947-51 (Box 19, Folder 563)
    - Kandinsky, Nina, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 564)
    - Kandinsky, Wassily, 1922-39, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 565-569)
    - Katibah, Mrs., 1925 (Box 20, Folder 570)
    - Keep America Out of War Congress, [1941] (Box 20, Folder 571)
    - Keith, Elizabeth, 1925, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 572)
    - Kelpe, Paul, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 573)
    - Keyser, Ragnhild, 1926 Apr 5 (Box 20, Folder 574)
    - Kiesler, Frederick, 1926-50, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 575-576)
      See also: Steffi Kiesler, box 20, folders 577-579
    - Kiesler, Steffi, 1927-50, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 577-579)
      See also: Frederick Kiesler, box 20, folders 575-576
    - Kingore Galleries (New York, N.Y.), 1923-29 (Box 20, Folder 580)
    - Kirchwey, Frida, 1926 (Box 20, Folder 581)
    - Klee, Paul, 1922-30, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 582)
    - Knapp, Lida, 1938 (Box 20, Folder 583)
    - Knaths, Karl, 1926-27 (Box 20, Folder 584)
    - Knoblauch, Mary, 1920-50, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 585-587)
    - Kölnischer Kunstverein, 1923-41, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 588-590)
    - Konta, Annie L., n.d. (Box 21, Folder 591)
    - Kopp, Marie E., 1940-41 (Box 21, Folder 592)
    - Kramár, Vincenc, 1927 Apr 11 (Box 21, Folder 593)
    - Kroch's International Bookstore, 1927 (Box 21, Folder 594)
    - Krotzer, Henry W., Jr., 1948, 1951 (Box 21, Folder 595)
    - Kubinyi, Victor de, 1926-27, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 596)
    - Kuh, Katharine, 1951 (Box 21, Folder 597)
    - Kuniyoshi, Yasuo, 1930, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 598)
    - Kunsthalle Bremen, 1932 (Box 21, Folder 599)
    - Kurtzworth, H. M., 1923-35, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 600)
    - "L" general, 1918-51, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 601)
    - Lachaise, Gaston, 1926 (Box 21, Folder 602)
    - Lamont, Corliss, 1943-44 (Box 21, Folder 603)
    - Landgren, Marchal E., 1949-50 (Box 21, Folder 604)
    - Lane, Charles J., 1929-30 (Box 21, Folder 605)
    - Lane, James W., 1935-36 (Box 21, Folder 606)
    - Langner, Lawrence, 1923 May 4 (Box 21, Folder 607)
    - Lasker, Bruno, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 608)
    - Lasker-Schüler, Else, 1920-21 (Box 21, Folder 609)
    - La Tour, Onya, 1939-50, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 610-612)
    - Lazzell, Blanche, 1925-38, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 613)
    - Leach, Agnes, 1925-33 (Box 21, Folder 614)
    - Leach, Henry Goddard
      See: Forum (New York, N.Y.), box 13, folder 366
    - League for Industrial Democracy, 1923, 1925 (Box 21, Folder 615)
    - League of Composers (U.S.), 1926, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 616)
    - Lee, Gerald Stanley, 1930, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 617)
    - Legal Aid Society (New York, N.Y.), n.d. (Box 22, Folder 618)
    - Léger, Fernand, 1924-31 (Box 22, Folder 619)
      See also: Oversize, box 118, folder 2795
    - Lehman, Robert, 1948 Feb 10 (Box 22, Folder 620)
      See also: Yale University Art Gallery Associates, box 40, folder 1138
    - Lehmann-Haupt, Hellmut, 1933 Nov 13 (Box 22, Folder 621)
    - Levitan, Jack
      See: Idee Fulkerson, box 13, folder 373
    - Levy, Florence Nightingale, 1947 (Box 22, Folder 622)
      See also: American Art Annual, box 2, folder 28
      See also: Arts Council of the City of New York, box 3, folders 78-81
      See also: Baltimore Museum of Art, box 4, folder 96
      See also: New York Art Calendar, box 27, folder 765
      See also: Box 83, folder 2075
    - Levy, Julien, 1940 Nov 18 (Box 22, Folder 623)
    - Lewis, W. S., 1941, 1950, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 624)
    - Library of Congress. Copyright Office, 1921-45, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 625)
    - Library of Congress. Periodicals Division, 1929 Sep 13 (Box 22, Folder 626)
    - Life, 1952 Jan 30 (Box 22, Folder 627)
    - Lincoln Warehouse Corporation, 1921-29 (Box 22, Folder 628)
    - Lindsay, Kenneth Clement, 1950 (Box 22, Folder 629)
    - Linné, Adolf, 1924-25, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 630)
    - Lins, Flora, 1923-45 (Box 22, Folder 631)
    - Lion, Louis, 1942-43 (Box 22, Folder 632)
    - Lion, Stephan C., 1942, 1945, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 633)
    - Lissitzky, El, 1926-27 (Box 22, Folder 634)
    - Lissitzky-Küppers, Sophie, 1926-27 (Box 22, Folder 635)
    - Litchfield, Edward H., 1918, 1928 (Box 22, Folder 636)
    - Litchfield, Marion, 1922, 1948, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 637)
    - Literary Digest, 1936 (Box 22, Folder 638)
    - Little Italy Neighborhood Association (Brooklyn, N.Y.), 1907-26, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 639-640)
    - Little Review, 1923-27, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 641)
    - Lohmann, Carl Albert
      See: Yale University Secretary, box 40, folder 1147
    - Lombardo, Josef Vincent, 1948 (Box 22, Folder 642)
    - Los Angeles City Schools, 1928 (Box 22, Folder 643)
    - Los Angeles County Museum, 1927 (Box 22, Folder 644)
    - Louchheim, Aline B.
      See: Aline B. Saarinen, box 31, folder 895
    - Loving, Pierre, 1921-35, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 645-646)
    - Lozinski, Bohdan Philip, 1948 (Box 22, Folder 647)
    - Lozowick, Louis, 1924-49, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 648-649)
    - Lubbers, Adriaan, 1937, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 650)
    - Lucien Lefebvre-Foinet, 1926-51, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 651-652)
    - Lydig, Rita de Acosta, 1920 (Box 23, Folder 653)
    - Lynn, Carol, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 654)